All right, so we finished three out of the four items.
我们现在已经完成了这四个步骤中的三个步骤
We have a list of word objects where each word is associated with an image.
我们具有一个 Word 对象列表 每个单词都与一个图片相关联
We have included all the images in the app, and
我们在应用中包含了所有的图片
we've updated list item layout to include an image view.
并且更新了列表项布局 使其包含图片视图
So now for task 4, we need to modify the instructions in the WordAdapter.
对于第 4 项任务 我们需要修改 WordAdapter 中的说明
The WordAdapter is responsible for
WordAdapter 负责
loading the right information from the word object into the list item layout,
将 Word 对象中的正确信息加载到列表项布局中
and this includes loading the right image into the image view.
包括将正确的图片加载到图片视图中
So going into our WordAdapter class, let's zero in on the getView method.
转到 WordAdapter 类 放大 getView 方法
Remember that this method gets called when the list view is trying to
当 ListView 尝试在给定位置显示项目列表时
display a list of items at a given position.
系统会调用该方法
So the list view will pass in a potential view that we could reuse.
ListView 将传入我们可能会重复使用的潜在视图
And here it's called convertView.
在这里 叫做 convertView
And the last input here refers to the parent view group for
最后一个输入指的是所有这些列表项的父 ViewGroup
all these list items which is the ListView itself.
即 ListView 本身
Now the purpose of the getView method is to return a list item view and
getView 方法旨在返回一个列表项视图
return it to the list view.
并返回给该 ListView
So the section of code here helps us inflate the view.
所以这部分代码可以帮助我们扩大该视图
So we inflate the list item view, meaning that we create a new list item
扩大列表项视图表示我们根据此 XML 资源“list_item”
layout from this XML resource list_item.
创建了一个新的列表项布局
And we're going to soar this in the list item view variable.
我们将在 ListItemView 变量中看到这个布局
I'm going to jump over toward this XML resources are cleared.
我将转到这个 XML 资源的声明部分
By right clicking going to Go to and then Declaration.
右击 选择“转到 (Go to)”然后选择“声明 (Declaration)”
So here in the XML resource, we see that though it's a single view,
在这个 XML 资源中 我们看到虽然它是单个视图
it's referencing the linear layout at the root of the layout.
但它引用了布局根部的线性布局
Well, from this view we can find the child views and modify them.
通过这个视图 我们能找到子视图 并修改这些视图
Now back to the WordAdapter.
现在回到 WordAdapter
This line of code here helps us get the word object
这行代码可以帮助我们在列表的给定位置
at the given position in the list.
获取 Word 对象
And then in this next section of code.,
然后在这部分代码中
we find the child text view with the ID miwork_ text_view and
我们找到 ID 为 miwok_text_view 的子 TextView
set the miwork translation of the word on to that text view.
将该单词的米沃克语翻译设置为该 TextView
And then repeat the same steps for the text view with ID default_text_view.
然后为 ID 是 default_text_view 的 TextView 执行相同的步骤
And set the English translation of the word on to the text view here.
并将该单词的英语翻译设置为此处的 TextView
And lastly since we've added an image view to our list item layout,
最后 因为我们已经向列表项布局添加图片视图
we'll need to make sure our adapters aware of that, too.
我们需要确保我们的适配器也知道这一点
For the next coding task, go ahead and modify the WordAdapter's get view
下一个编程任务是修改 WordAdapter 的 getView 方法
method, so it sets the right image into ImageView of the list item layout.
使其将正确的图片设置到列表项布局的 ImageView 中
And as a hint, refer to the Android flavor app as an example.
提示下 请参考 Android Flavor 应用
As a hint, you can refer to the Android flavor app from the last lesson if
你可以参考上节课中的 Android Flavor 应用
that helps.
或许有帮助
So this app remember displays an image for
这个应用在每个列表项中为对应的
the corresponding Android release in each list item.
Android 版本都显示了一个图片
So this is what the new walk app should look like when you're done.
当你操作完毕后 Miwok 应用应该是这样的
So notice that there's a problem with the phrases activity, but
注意 PhrasesActivity 现在还存在问题
we're going to fix that in a later code step.
但是我们将在后续编程步骤中解决该问题
So don't worry about that for this task.
对于该任务 不用担心该问题